otcmarkets.com 2013-12-31

# Privacy Statement - OTCMarkets.com

OTC Markets Group does not collect any personally identifiable information from the users of this site.

We gather information during normal browsing that we do not tie back to a specific individual user. Like the operators of many other websites, OTC Markets Group receives and collects information about your session, including the IP (internet protocol) address, domain name, browser type, operating system you use, the files you download, pages you visit and dates/times of those visits. This information about your session or about you may be collected by technology such as, "cookies" and "web beacons". We only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally.

### Cookies

There is a technology called "cookies," which are small text files that a website transfers to a user's hard disk or browser. Cookies can be used by a website to enable its users to store tailored information from the website. Whenever you interact with our website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, “cookie” information, and the page you requested. These cookies act as identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Because cookies are simple text and not "executable," a cookie will not give your computer a virus or other harmful program.

You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit its acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our website’s features. Our advertising partners, which may include advertisers, advertising agencies, and ad networks, may also transmit cookies to your computer or device, when you view or interact with one of their ads that appear on our website. Also, if you click on a link to a third party website, such third party may also transmit cookies to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties other than third party advertisers.

### Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. The privacy statements of the third-party advertising companies we use can be accessed from <http://www.rubiconproject.com/privacy/>, <http://privacy.aol.com/> and <http://www.openx.com/about/openx-market-privacy-principles>. Third party advertisers often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

### Contact Us

We use email links located on the "contact us" page to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly to every one. This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also file your comments to improve the site and program, or review and discard the information. Your personal information is only shared with third parties with your explicit permission.

### Logged Files

The www.otcmarkets.com website logs IP addresses and browser types for systems administration purposes and these logs will be analyzed to constantly improve the value of the materials available on the website. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that OTC Markets Group is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
